从日志中，我们知道我们拥有了正确的forecast数据，
From the logs, we know that we have the right forecast
并且它是我们希望的正确格式。
data and it's in the right format that we want as
因此最后，我们需要更新UI。
an array of strings. So it's finally time to update the
想想怎样AsyncTasks能够将数据传回
UI. Think back on how AsyncTasks are able to pass data
给主线程。你能够打入Ctrl+O看看
back onto the main thread. You can hit Ctrl+O to see
我们还能重写AsyncTask的哪些方法。如果
the list of available methods we can override in AsyncTask. If
你点击它们中的任何一个，他将产生
you click on any of them, it will be prepopulated in
在代码中。然后，你能使用从AsyncTask接收到的新的数据去更新ArrayAdapter。
the code for you. Then, you can update ArrayAdapter with the new
作为一个提示，
data that was retrieved by the AsyncTask. As a hint, you
你能够将ForecastAdapter作为全局变量。这样的话，你
can make the ForecastAdapter be a global variable. That way, you
能够在FetchWeatherTask中访问到它。确保这
can access it from within the FetchWeatherTask. Make sure that this
不是一个静态类，否则，你将不能
is not a static class, otherwise, you won't be able to
访问forecast fragment中的成员变量。然后，
access the member variable from the forecast fragment. Then, go ahead
编译和构建你的应用。当你运行它时，
and compile and build the app. When you run it, and
你点击refresh按钮，你应该看到你所在地区的一个星期的
you hit the refresh button, you should see a week's worth
天气数据。一旦它运行了，你可以
of weather data for your location. Once it's working, you can
删除verbose日志语句，以至于日志不会那么
remove the verbose log statements so you don't
杂乱。当你运行这个代码，
clutter the logs. As you're working on this
如果你看到了unsupported operation异常，
code, if you see an unsupported operation exception,
确保当你创建假数据时，
make sure that when you're creating the fake
当你初始化ArrayAdapter时，你传入了一个字符串列表，
data, that when you initialize ArrayAdapter, you passed
而不是
in a list of strings, and not an
一个数组。这样你能够在这个list集合中调用clear方法或者add方法。
array. That way you can call the clear
method or the add method on this list collection.